(Previously) This is the letter
that someone sent to my mother,
tricking her into coming
down from the village.
Can you find out who did this?
Why are you trying
to dig up the past?
The one who is most
at fault is your father.
This is clearly murder.
We barely have any evidence left to
help us convict the culprit.
But we have that letter.
The Kusuma people.
About your mother, I won't stop searching.
No matter how long it takes, I will find her.
I love you, Dad. And I love Gaysorn too.
Dad, can you please tell me?
What am I supposed to do, Dad?
Dad!
Tell me!
What do I have to do to get your scent?
I told you that you can't!
Stop lying to me!
Tell me! Tell me now!
What is the secret? Tell me!
Anurak? Hey!
Hey!
"Flower Boy" (Episode 8)
Dad?
You're fine now.
Doctor said that you're safe now.
What do you want to tell me?
Camera?
Is it camera?
Yes.
What camera?
House?
Our house?
I got the letter when I went to the market.
People passed it along so I didn't know
who the sender was.
The sender must have known
Gaysorn's mom really well.
They knew where she was
and what to do to get
her to leave the moutains.
Who would know the details
unless they worked with Gaysorn's dad?
Scent's dad and uncle.
Scent lured Gaysorn to the city
because he wanted to bring
back Bussaba's scent, didn't he?
If that's the case, then
one of them killed my mom.
Or both of them.
Gaysorn gave Scent the letter.
Gaysorn, you need to call Scent now.
Put him on speaker phone.
He didn't pick up the phone.
What should I do?
The letter is the only
evidence that I have.
He's calling.
I'm sorry, I was busy.
I saw your call, what is it?
I'd like to ask you about the letter.
Did you find out who sent the letter?
Scent?
What is it?
Hey, are you okay?
We need to meet up.
I want to talk to you in person.
Where are you?
I need the letter back.
I kept the letter at home.
How about this?
Can we talk at my place?
Give me two hours,
I need to sort things out about my dad.
What is your plan?
I need to get the letter back first.
Then what?
Should we expose him?
I can call the reporters.
People need to know about
them using people for making perfume.
They're so doomed.
You can't do that.
The outsiders will know
about the Mudan scent.
What are we going to do?
We don't have enough
evidence to go to the police.
Even if we report to the police,
it will end up in news eventually.
It is up to you, Gaysorn.
What do you want?
I know that
I can't put him in jail.
But at least, he needs to own up for it,
that he hurt my mom.
Hello, Scent.
Yeah, I'm inside the house.
Hello, Mr. Sun.
Nobody's home. Can I help you?
Scent asked me to get
something from the house.
Hello, Mr. Scent?
Sure. Got it.
- This way, sir.
- Right.
- Hello, Scent?
- How was it? Did you find it?
Yeah, I got it with me.
Good, you need to deliver
it to the hospital right now.
You got it, pal.
Mr. Ray? Mr. Mekin?
Is Wittaya home?
He hasn't been here yet.
Cool, we're going to wait inside.
Wait! Hey! What do you mean?
Where are you going?
We will wait for him.
I think you better let us wait here nicely.
- Come here!
- Hey! What is this?
Why are you here? Hey!
Why are there so many of you here?
We need to talk.
About my mother.
There is nothing to say.
Get out of my house! Now!
No!
What?
- Let's go.
- Hey!
Hey!
Let me go!
- Hello?
- Mr. Scent!
Someone took Mr. Wittaya.
What? Who took him?
Mr. Ray, Mr. Mekin
and three other people.
But they dressed differently than us.
Gaysorn?
Get out! Come here!
What the hell is this?
What is it?
Where are you taking me?
What the hell is this?
You killed my mom
and buried her here.
I didn't do it.
You can't blame me without any evidence.
- We have the evidence.
- What evidence?
The letter that you wrote to fool Bussaba
to leave the mountains.
The letter?
We need to meet up.
I want to talk to you in person.
Where are you?
I need the letter back.
I kept the letter at home.
How about this?
Can we talk at my place?
Give me two hours,
I need to sort things out about my dad.
The letter?
What letter?
There is no letter.
Where is the letter?
There is no more letter for you.
Mr. Ray? Mr. Mekin?
Is Wittaya home?
He hasn't been here yet.
Cool, we're going to wait inside.
Let's go.
Wait! Hey! What do you mean?
Where are you going?
[The maid]
Why is she calling me?
You don't have any
evidence to incriminate anyone.
You should let me go
or I will press charges
for illegal confinement.
Nobody can own up to this?
What?
Tawan!
Tawan! No!
I will kill him!
He deserves to die after
what he did to Gaysorn's mom.
No! Tawan!
I don't care. I will kill him.
He killed Gaysorn's mom,
how could I let him go?
I didn't kill Bussaba.
The person who killed Bussaba is my brother.
It's Scent's dad.
Where are you going?
Tawan! That's enough!
Was it Scent's dad? Really?
That's right.
His dad was obsessed with making
the perfume and he lost his mind.
He really wanted to come up
with a perfume with your mom's scent.
So he kept her in a room
and tortured her until she died.
He is my own brother
so I needed to bring her dead body
to bury right here.
When I see you all react like this,
I feel bad for you.
And I feel bad for what happened.
But my brother already
paid for what he did.
So what?
You're not satisfied with that?
Are you going to put a
bedridden person in jail?
I'm not going to stop you,
you should do what you want.
Stop lying already.
Scent?
You think nobody would find out
that you were the cause of
what happened to Bussaba?
What did I do?
Gaysorn,
this is the clip that my dad recorded
before he became like this.
I am Anurak Sukontawanich.
I can't take it any longer.
I keep seeing Bussaba in my head
but she was already gone.
She is dead.
It's because of Wittaya,
he accidentally killed her.
Wittaya was obsessed with Bussaba's scent
and he accidentally pushed
Pruek down the stairs.
He also tricked Bussaba
to leave the mountains
so I can start my experiments on her,
hoping to recreate Bussaba's scent.
Wittaya said that
this scent will be our future.
Without the scent,
Bussaba will be done for.
We forced her
until one day
she was dead.
You lied to me.
You blamed it on my dad
when you were the one who killed her!
You killed Gaysorn's parents.
All you got is this clip.
You dad lost his mind back then.
His words can't be trusted.
Your dad killed them, not me.
Sure, if you said so.
I guess you remember
what happened in this clip as well.
Where are you going?
Why are you crying?
Help! Help!
Stop moving! Stop it!
I told you to stay still!
Stay still! Come on!
Wittaya?
She's dead.
Here.
You should do whatever you want to.
I will take care of the rest.
How could you do this to me!? Scent!
How could you do this to your family?
You ungrateful son of a bitch!
I have to, uncle.
I have to.
Mr. Wittaya Sukontawanich.
You are a suspect of a homicide
and concealment of the body.
Please go to the police station to testify.
Follow me.
Please get in.
I'm proud of you
for doing the right thing.
I'm sorry
for what my uncle and dad did
to your parents.
I'm sorry for everything
that I have ever done to you.
I know that you won't forgive me.
Please go back to Mudan.
This place is to cruel for you.
I'm not the guy for you.
And I…
I don't deserve you.
I'm sorry.
Scent.
Thank you.
Mata,
what is going to happen next?
It will depend
on both of them after this.
Dad,
Uncle Wittaya was arrested.
You don't have to worry.
The police said that
you should recover first.
Yeah?
What are you trying to say?
I…
I'm sorry.
Sorry.
It's okay.
I'll be here with you no matter what.
I won't go anywhere.
I will be here will you.
Give me the flowers, Tawan.
Mom.
You should rest here
so you can watch sunrise before anyone.
Mudan people
are just like flowers,
daylight, and dew.
We will embrace you.
You can finally rest in peace, Bussaba.
Is it still working?
It won't work up here.
Mekin said that there's no signal.
It means that
if the city people try to contact us,
we won't know about it, right?
Are you going to be fine?
Mudan people are like flowers.
Our place is right here in the mountains.
I can't live anywhere else.
You miss him?
Nope. I was just scrolling through my album.
Why don't you go to see him?
You don't remember what they said?
They don't want us to be involved.
And they want their Mudan
tribe to remain a secret.
More importantly, I don't miss him at all.
- Really?
- Yes.
I think that he's cute
and I wanted to pick on Scent.
You don't have to pick on him.
He has always been working in the lab.
So pathetic.
I want it to feel like
standing amidst a
wildflower field in the north,
and flowers are blooming.
The base should be
pine leaves,
and the flowers should be
roses and cape jasmine.
Let's try.
It's done, why don't you test it?
How is it, Scent?
Sun, I want it to have a smell of the sea.
The sea?
Yeah, warm like the sea.
Okay.
What do you think?
Okay,
but can I ask you to add one more?
- What is it?
- I want it to be like…
a park in the city.
But we will mix three themes in one bottle.
The scents won't blend together,
there are too many different layers.
Come on, just try it.
Fine, fine.
The park?
It should be grass with moss,
mixing with plumeria.
Let's do it.
How is it?
I think it is still missing something.
What type of scent?
Good question.
Peony.
Peony?
What does 'Mudan' mean?
It means peony.
It symbolizes prosperity,
honor,
and…
innocent love.
Mudan.
How many drops?
One drop.
I'm with Mr. Scent
and the most hyped perfume at this moment.
I'm talking about the 'Gaysorn'
perfume from Kusuma.
Thank you everyone for
your support of our perfume.
I took a sniff and I must tell you that
this perfume is quite something.
It contains different layers
and I needed to ask Mr. Scent
about the inspirations behind
the creation of this perfume.
The perfume
is an extract of your preserved memoies.
I named it 'Gaysorn'
because I believe that scent
is a form of contact.
It's more than a touch of your skin
but it's a touch of memories
that are stored deep
down in your heart.
It will remind you of good
and unforgettable memories.
Also, it will remind you of love.
No matter where you are in this world,
love will remain in your heart
and it will never fade away.
- Fire! Fire!
- Hey!
Gaysorn! What happened? Move!
Who told you to put foil in the microwave?
You did.
You told me to just put it in.
What?
It burned!
Do you think I can eat it?
Which one looks yummier?
I think…
This one.
Can I have a bite?
Sure.
In this capital increase agreement,
Mekin will hold more shares,
up to 15% of Kusuma.
It is valued at 120 million baht.
The conditions
will follow the same agreement
as what's been drafted.
If you all are ready,
please sign on both copies.
What's wrong with your
hand? What did you do?
It's nothing.
Happy Birthday to You.
Happy Birthday!
Make a wish.
I wish…
we'll become a real couple. Can we?
Sure.
Hello, Julie.
I see.
You can send it to me now.
We can't make any mistakes
with our partners in Europe.
If you finish with the revised version,
you can send it to me.
I'll send you the reference for checking.
Scent? Are you okay?
You look so pale.
I'm fine.
Just a little dizzy.
I need to use a bathroom.
Are you okay?
Scent! Hey!
Scent! Scent!
Scent!
Who's here? Scent!
Gaysorn! Gaysorn!
Gaysorn!
- Gaysorn!
- Tawan?
What's the matter?
I went to the market earlier
and I saw Mekin.
He wanted to see you.
He said that he will wait for you
at the national park's office.
It's noon already.
Are you sure that Gaysorn will be here?
See?
We were just wondering if you'd show up.
Hey,
he's not coming.
He wanted you to have this.
This is a perfume that Scent developed
because he misses you.
He misses you a lot.
I want it to feel like
standing amidst a
wildflower field in the north.
A scent to remind you of park in the city.
A scent of the sea,
the warmth of the sea.
Mudan means peony.
It symbolizes prosperity,
honor,
and…
innocent love.
I think…
Scent isn't the only one who loves Gaysorn.
Gaysorn loves Scent so much as well.
Why isn't he here?
It's not like he didn't want to come,
but he couldn't be here.
What's wrong with him?
Where is Scent?
I'm not dreaming, am I?
Is this real enough for you?
I never thought you'd be back.
Your perfume
told me to come back to you.
It really is you. It's you.
I missed you.
I bought this plot of land
because it is close to the mountains.
When I missed you,
I would plant flowers here.
You did?
That's right.
And I will keep on planting them.
Because I will miss you forever.
Hey!
What?
I don't think you need to plant any flowers.
Why's that?
When we stay together,
why would you miss me?
Really?
Gaysorn,
I love you.
And I…
You don't have to ell me.
You scent tells it all.
You love me too, don't you?
[The end.]